fxtrek.com 2003-06-08

# Privacy Policy -- FXtrek.com

_**Voluntary Submissions**_  
FXtrek.com’s registration form asks users to voluntarily provide us with contact information such as street address, e-mail, telephone number, as well as demographic information. The mailing address and credit card numbers are required only for FXtrek subscribers for credit card processing purposes, and NO secondary correspondences will be sent to them via US mail. We use the information to help us improve our services, to provide you with products and services you have requested, and to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you (see the E-mail Communications section). We will not disclose or share the information with any third party without your permission. Users may opt-out of receiving future e-mails (see the choice/opt-out section below). 

Our online surveys ask visitors for financial information and demographic information (like their age, or income level). This information is used on an aggregate basis only. Complying with the recently passed Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect personal information for children under 13. For details of COPPA, please visit <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm> and  
<http://www.ftc.gov/opa/1999/9910/childfinal.htm>

_**Cookies**_  
A cookie is a small data file containing certain information and is written to your hard drive when you visit the web-site. A cookie cannot be read by a web-site other than the one that sets the cookie. Most cookies last only through a single session or visit. 

Currently, FXtrek.com only offers cookies capturing User Name (but not password) to registered users so they do not have to re-enter each time they want to login to the site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. If your browser is set to reject cookies, you might need to login each time an access-controlled page is requested. 

_**Public Forums**_  
This site makes forums and message boards available to its users. While the system will display only your screen-name automatically when you post messages, please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

_**Personal Portfolio Security**_  
All portfolio data is secured at FXtrek.com. We will not examine the contents of your portfolio unless a problem occurs and we are given the permission from you. Under no circumstances will the contents of the users' portfolios be shared with any third parties. 

_**Log Files**_  
While our web servers automatically log information such as IP addresses, browser types and access times, we do not link that information to personal identification information. These log files are kept and analyzed for web-site activity reports on aggregate basis only. 

_**E-mail Communications**_  
E-mail addresses are required in order to register as a subscriber with FXtrek.com. We do not rent or sell our subscribers' e-mail addresses to third parties. Occasionally, we will send e-mail to our existing users to provide information that we think is useful, including information about our new products and services. Our users have the option of removing their addresses from the mailing list to avoid future e-mail communications or to no longer receive our services (See the Choice/Opt-Out section). When we receive e-mails from our users for various issues, the correspondences are only kept until the issues are resolved and we do not retain addresses for mailing purposes. 

_**Security**_  
FXtrek.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We also use advanced encryption protocols to protect your sensitive information, such as your credit card numbers when they are sent over the Internet. No sensitive data is stored on any publicly accessible server and the access to that information is restricted to only the related employees with certain level of passwords. 

A good understanding of our security policy is required for each employee of FXtrek.com and we review our security policy and measures on weekly basis. 

_**Billing and Credit Card Information**_  
The secured servers of AuthorizeNet.com handle the billing transactions for the FXtrek subscriptions. For more information, please visit its website at [http://www.authorizenet.com](http://www.authorizenet.com/). 

_**Choice/ Opt-Out**_  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. Users can also send email to [webmaster@FXtrek.com](mailto:webmaster@FXTrek.com) for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

_**Correct/Update**_  
Users can modify information previously provided online following the link from the "Update Information" tag on the "Member Service" tool bar or by sending email to [webmaster@FXtrek.com](mailto:webmaster@FXtrek.com). 

_**Notification of Change on Privacy Policy**_  
This Privacy Policy might be modified from time to time. In the case that we plan to use the information collected from the user differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will post appropriate notice at our web-site or send e-mails to the affected users, so they will have the opportunity to opt-out. 

_**Contacting the Website**_  
If you wish to learn more about FXtrek.com’s efforts to protect your privacy, please feel free to send questions and comments to: [info@FXtrek.com](mailto:info@FXtrek.com)
